Elizaveta Uvarova

Frontend Developer

Yerevan, Armenia

+37491186660

uvarovaes2002@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizaveta-uvarova42/

ABOUT

I am a Frontend Developer with good knowledges of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React, passionate about software development. Also I have beginner design skills, worked with Figma.

Currently I'm searching for Frontend or JavaScript Developer job where I can grow and improve my skills.

I can work in Yerevan or remotely.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer

Freelance

nov 2022 - jan 2023

- Developed responsive website using HTML, SCSS, JavaScript
- Worked with a team of developers using GitLab
- Fixed bags

Web Designer

Freelance

sep 2021 - dec 2021

- · Planned site design, functionality and navigation
- Designed service for the selection of computer components
- Made website responsive
- · Worked collaboratively with developers to make sleek UI design

EDUCATION

Ural State Technical University Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Software Engineer

sep 2020 - Present

CERTIFICATIONS

Sololearn

JavaScript course

2022

Sololearn

jQuery course

2022

Coursera

HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers

2022

Coursera

Introduction to Web Development

2022

Sololearn

React + Redux course

2022

PROJECTS

You can see my pet-projects here: https://github.com/ElizavetaUv and here: https://www.figma.com/@elizavetauv

LANGUAGES

- English B1+
- Russian Native

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- JavaScript
- React
- Redax
- jQuery
- BEM
- Git
- Python
- Figma

SOFT SKILLS

- Fast learning ability
- Self-learning
- Team player
- Adaptability
- Responsibility